let MyQuestions = [{
    question: "Which video game was the first video game played in space during the 1990’s?",
    options: ["Pac Man", "Tetris", "Uno", "Super Mario"],
    answer: "Tetris",
},
{
    question: "Tamagotchi’s were all the rage in the 1990’s. But what do the two Japanese words translate to?",
    options: ["Rice and Beans", "Salt and Vinegar", "Egg and Friend", "Eletronic and Friend"],
    answer: "Egg and Friend",
},
 {
     question: "What was the name of the furry toy, popular throughout the 1990’s, that some people thought was spying on them?",
     options: ["Furby", "Barbie", "Ted", "Care Bears"],
     answer: "Furby",
 },
 {
     question: "The Channel Tunnel is an underwater tunnel that connects the UK and France. When was it opened?",
     options: ["1984", "1994", "1997", "1988"],
     answer: "1994",
 },
 {
     question: "Mike Tyson infamously bit part of someone’s ear off in a boxing match in 1997. Who had their ear bitten by Tyson?",
     options: ["Muhammad Ali", "Evander Holyfield", "Roberto Duran", "Rocky Balboa"],
     answer: "Evander Holyfield",
 },
 {
     question: "What was the most popular cellphone of the 1990’s?",
     options: ["iPhone", "Siemens S10", "Motorola StarTAC", "Nokia 3210"],
     answer: "Nokia 3210",
 },
 {
     question: "Casio made an iconic style of watch during the 1990’s. What was it called?",
     options: ["Super Illuminator", "Royale", "G-Shock", "Calculator Watch"],
     answer: "G-Shock",
 },
 {
     question: "What is the name of the accessory you would have worn on the outside of your jeans?",
     options: ["A wallet chain", "A flannel shirt", "A bandanna", "Discman headphones"],
     answer: "A wallet chain",
 },
 {
     question: "Who released the chart-topping song Wannabe in 1996?",
     options: ["Spice Girls", "Backstreet Boys", "NSYNC", "Enya"],
     answer: "Spice Girls",
 },
 {
     question: "What did the band REM end up losing in their 1991 single?",
     options: ["Their Faith", "Their Fame", "Their Voice", "Their Religion"],
     answer: "Their Religion",
 },
 {
    question: "What video game console was the best-selling console of the 1990’s?",
    options: ["Sony Playstation", "Xbox", "Nintendo", "Sega"],
    answer:"Sony Playstation",
 },
 {
    question: "What year was the World Wide Web first introduced?",
    options: ["1990", "1992", "1991", "1993"],
    answer:"1991",
 },
 {
    question: "Which website was first introduced in 1998?",
    options: ["Facebook", "YouTube", "Google", "Orkut"],
    answer:"Google",
 },
 {
    question: "In the 1990’s, scientists managed to clone a sheep. What was the sheep’s name?",
    options: ["Mary", "Anna", "Dolly", "Dorothy"],
    answer:"Dolly",
 },
 {
    question: "Pokemon was a cultural phenomenon (and still is today). What does Pikachu evolve into?",
    options: ["Raichu", "Jigglypuff", "Machoke", "Rapidash"],
    answer:"Raichu",
 },
 {
    question: "What was one of the most popular ways to contact someone during the 1990’s?",
    options: ["Send a letter", "Smoke signals", "Using a pager", "Drums"],
    answer:"Using a pager",
 },
 {
    question: "What is the name of the fashion accessory worn by women around the neck?",
    options: ["Belts", "Necklaces", "Chokers", "Bracelets"],
    answer:"Chokers",
 },
 {
    question: "What patterned shirt was popularized by bands like Nirvana and *NSYNC?",
    options: ["Croche shirts", "Leather shirts", "Denim shirts", "Flannel shirts"],
    answer:"Flannel shirts",
 },
 {
    question: "What was the name of the ballad released by Extreme in 1991?",
    options: ["Play with Me", "Hole Hearted", "More Than Words", "He-Man Woman Hater"],
    answer:"More Than Words",
 },
 {
    question: "The band Semisonic were a one-hit-wonder from the 1990’s. What was their hit called?",
    options: ["Closing Time", "Closing Doors", "Closing Relationships", "Closing Deals"],
    answer:"Closing Time",
 },
 {
    question: "Smells Like Teen Spirit is an iconic song from the 1990’s. What is it inadvertently about?",
    options: ["Deodorant", "Shampoo", "Conditioner", "Soap"],
    answer:"Deodorant",
 },
 {
    question: "Who came up with the name ‘*NSYNC’?",
    options: ["JC Chasez's mon", "Joey Fatone's mom", "Justin Timberlake’s mom", "Lance Bass's mom"],
    answer:"Justin Timberlake’s mom",
 },
 {
    question: "How many members did popular boyband Backstreet Boys have?",
    options: ["6", "3", "5", "4"],
    answer:"5",
 },
 {
    question: "What is the name of the band that released a song about Barbie, who were also sued by Mattel?",
    options: ["Ocean", "River", "Aqua", "Sea"],
    answer:"Aqua",
 },
 {
    question: "What single did Christina Aguilera hit the top spot on the Billboard Hot 100 with?",
    options: ["Genie In A Bottle", "What a Girl Wants", "I Turn to You", "Come On Over Baby (All I Want Is You)"],
    answer:"Genie In A Bottle",
 },
 {
    question: "Who wrote the song ‘Nothing Compares to You’, which Sinead O’Connor had a hit with in 1990?",
    options: ["Elton John", "Queen", "Prince", "ABBA"],
    answer:"Prince",
 },
 {
    question: "Which two British bands are commonly put into the genre bracket of Britpop and were rivals throughout the 1990’s?",
    options: ["The Verve and Take That", "Oasis and Blur", "Keane and Radiohead", "Five and S Club 7"],
    answer:"Oasis and Blur",
 },
 {
    question: "What is Woody and Buzz Lightyear’s owner called in Toy Story?",
    options: ["Mike", "Andy", "Daniel", "Conan"],
    answer:"Andy",
 },
 {
    question: "Which film was the highest-grossing film of 1994?",
    options: ["The Lion King", "A Bug's Life", "Hercules", "Aladdin"],
    answer:"The Lion King",
 },
 {
    question: "Which movie, released in 1997, was the first movie to gross more than $1 billion?",
    options: ["Jurassic Park", "Titanic", "Liar Liar", "Men in Black"],
    answer:"Titanic",
 },
 {
    question: "What is the name of the film that McCauley Culkin got $1 million for?",
    options: ["My Girl", "Home Alone", "Richie Rich", "The Good Son"],
    answer:"My Girl",
 },
 {
    question: "What was the first animated feature film to nominated for a Best Picture Oscar?",
    options: ["Beauty and the Beast", "The Lion King", "Mulan", "Pocahontas"],
    answer:"Beauty and the Beast",
 },
 {
    question: "Power Rangers was banned in what country until 2011?",
    options: ["Ireland", "Brazil", "New Zealand", "Australia"],
    answer:"New Zealand",
 },
 {
    question: "Genetic engineering introduced what color roses for the first time?",
    options: ["Red", "Green", "Blue", "Yellow"],
    answer:"Blue",
 },
 {
    question: "What classic Audrey Hepburn film was the title of a 1995 one-hit wonder?",
    options: ["Breakfast at Tiffany's", "Roman Holiday", "My Fair Lady", "Sabrina"],
    answer:"Breakfast at Tiffany's",
 },
 {
    question: "Any true 90s aficionado should immediately know the band of brothers behind the hit “MMMBop”?",
    options: ["Hanson", "Backstreet Boys", "NSYNC", "S Club 7"],
    answer:"Hanson",
 },
 {
    question: "This video store chain was a wall street giant right up until it was swallowed whole by the emergence of Netflix and streaming?",
    options: ["Ghostbusters", "Blockbuster", "100% Video", "Genius Video"],
    answer:"Blockbuster",
 },
 {
    question: "In classrooms in the days before flat screen TVs, teachers would utilize clear transparent paper and these devices to show their classes work on a white board?",
    options: ["Interactive Whiteboards", "Mimeograph", "Overhead Projectors", "Multifunction Copiers and Printers"],
    answer:"Overhead Projectors",
 },
 {
    question: "This winner of 7 academy awards focused on Liam Neeson as he tried to trick Nazis during WW2 to save the lives of hundreds of Jewish innocents?",
    options: ["The Thin Red Line", "Memphis Belle", "Schindler’s List", "Saving Private Ryan"],
    answer:"Schindler’s List",
 },
 {
    question: "Mel Gibson plays famed historical warrior William Wallace in this 90s action epic?",
    options: ["The Patriot", "Braveheart", "Maverick", "Conspiracy Theory"],
    answer:"Braveheart",
 },
 {
    question: "One of the greatest twists of all time in film, this film’s most memorable quote is “I see dead people”?",
    options: ["The 6th Sense", "Tha Past Tense", "The Common Sense", "The Sense 8"],
    answer:"The 6th Sense",
 },
 {
   question: "Featuring the most sensual clay shaping scene in history, this film featured Patrick Swayze and a haunted Demi Moore?",
    options: ["Phantom", "Ghost", "Spirit", "Apparition"],
    answer:"Ghost",
 },
 {
    question: "A brilliant play on Plato’s “Allegory of the Cave”, this film bended minds with Keanu Reeves in 1999?",
    options: ["Tha Array", "The Grid", "The Matrix", "The Table"],
    answer:"The Matrix",
 },
 {
    question: "Which country won the World Cup in 1994?",
    options: ["Brazil", "Argentina", "Paraguay", "Chile"],
    answer:"Brazil",
 },
 {
    question: "New York city was the backdrop for this wildly popular 90s comedy which launched the careers of stars like Jennifer Aniston, Courtney Cox and Matthew Perry?",
    options: ["Friends", "BFF", "Familiar", "Colleague"],
    answer:"Friends",
 },
 {
    question: "Maybe the original “teen drama”, this show revolutionized television by tackling prickly topics like addiction, eating disorders, teen pregnancy and more as it spawned a generation of copycats?",
    options: ["Beverly Hills, 90210", " Los Angeles, 90210", "San Diego, 90210", "San Francisco, 90210"],
    answer:"Beverly Hills, 90210",
 },
 {
    question: "This 90s brunette heart throb starred in films like I Know What You Did Last Summer, and Can’t Hardly Wait?",
    options: ["Jennifer Love Hewitt", "Jennifer Lawrence", "Jennifer Aniston", "Jennifer Connelly"],
    answer:"Jennifer Love Hewitt",
 },
 {
    question: "“Waterfalls” is the most well known song by this iconic R&B group?",
    options: ["Total", "SWV", "TLC", "En Vogue"],
    answer:"TLC",
 },
 {
    question: "This latin heart throb was a 90s sensation with his hit that translates to “Living the Crazy Life”?",
    options: ["Luis Miguel", "Enrique Iglesias", "Ricky Martin", "Alejandro Sanz"],
    answer:"Ricky Martin",
 },
 {
    question: "The horrifying mass shooting at this high school in Colorado would sadly be the first many mass casualty incidents in US Schools?",
    options: ["Silver Creek", "Skyline", "Peak to Peak", "Columbine"],
    answer:"Columbine",
 }
];